<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="month2html.xsl"?>

<linkfarm>

<link url="http://prdownloads.sourceforge.net/owasp/OWASPWebApplicationSecurityTopTen-Version1.pdf"
      time="2003-01-13T15:37-08:00"
      title="The Ten Most Critical Web Application Security Vulnerabilities">
  <source url="http://www.owasp.org/" title="The Open Web Application Security Project"/>
  <archive date="2003-01-13"
           rurl="prdownloads.sourceforge.net/owasp/OWASPWebApplicationSecurityTopTen-Version1.pdf"/>
  <description>
    A new report detailing the ten most critical web application security
    problems. The security issues raised here are not new. In fact, some have
    been well understood for decades. Yet for some reason, major software
    development projects are still making these mistakes and jeopardizing not
    only their customers' security, but also the security of the entire
    Internet.
  </description>
  <comment>
    If you do any web development that goes beyond static HTML, you better be
    familiar with every issue raised in this report. Otherwise, you're just
    asking for your web server to be hacked into.
  </comment>
</link>

<link url="http://www.redherring.com/insider/2003/01/copycats011003.html"
      time="2003-01-12T04:33-08:00"
      title="What lawyers can learn from comic books">
  <source url="http://www.redherring.com/" title="Red Herring">
    <via url="http://grep.law.harvard.edu/article.pl?sid=03/01/10/2153219"
         title="GrepLaw"/>
  </source>
  <archive date="2003-01-12"
           rurl="www.redherring.com/insider/2003/01/copycats011003.html"/>
  <description>
    Forty percent of publications produced in Japan are comics, which provide
    30 percent of Japanese publishing revenue. But the comics, or manga,
    market in Japan is divided into two types: one is purely original work;
    the other is "amateur" or copycat comics, which develop the work of
    original artists in different and unauthorized ways. This second kind of
    comic, called dojinshi , is a huge and growing market in Japan.<br />
    Put most simply, however, dojinshi is illegal. So what is it that accounts
    for this massive "theft" of the creative work of original manga artists?
    Why is this "invasion" of the "rights of creators" allowed?
  </description>
  <comment>
    Concise and to the point. As much as certain activities might be illegal,
    such as copyright infringement, companies should consider the business
    consequences of actually pursuing a lawsuit against the transgressors.
    This is especially true when the "illegal" activities are actually
    improving the company's bottom line by increasing consumer interest and/or
    satisfaction.<br />
    I can't believe that someone actually has to write about this! Is our
    country so ready to sue that they don't even consider the practicality of
    what they're doing? Another reason why jury nullification makes sense:
    did you just break the letter of the law, or did you actually cause harm
    to some person/corporation?
  </comment>
</link>

<link url="http://www.aclu.org/cartoons/artshow.html"
      time="2003-01-12T04:23-08:00"
      title="USA PATRIOT Art Show">
  <source url="http://www.aclu.org/" title="American Civil Liberties Union">
    <via url="http://boingboing.net/2003_01_01_archive.html#90169036"
         title="Boing Boing"/>
  </source>
  <description>
    In the aftermath of September 11, freedom of speech has been under attack.
    Political cartoonists are not immune. In some cities cartoonists have
    been fired or lost freelance jobs because of cartoons critical of U.S.
    policy or for using "wrong" metaphors.<br />
    In response, cartoonists Gary Huck, Mike Konopacki, Matt Wuerker and
    writer Alec Dubro put together a show of cartoons from 41 editorial
    cartoonists from the U.S. and Mexico.
  </description>
  <comment>
    Great "virtual" exhibition of political cartoons. I just wish they'd
    included even more of them.
  </comment>
</link>

<link url="http://www.openp2p.com/pub/a/p2p/2002/12/11/piracy.html"
      time="2003-01-10T01:33-08:00"
      title="Piracy is Progressive Taxation, and Other Thoughts on the Evolution of Online Distribution">
  <source url="http://www.openp2p.com/" title="OpenP2P.com"/>
  <archive date="2003-01-10"
           rurl="www.openp2p.com/pub/a/p2p/2002/12/11/piracy.html"/>
  <description>
    As he follows the business world of movies and music, Tim O'Reilly draws
    upon his own publishing experience and comments on the current
    controversy over digital file sharing.
  </description>
  <comment>
    Tim O'Reilly doesn't really make a strong point about anything in
    particular, but a good rehashing/summary of the best arguments from
    the pro-file-sharing camp. Basically, an author would rather have
    his work pirated widely than live in obscurity; consumers will pay for
    fairly priced, added value services rather than download free, but
    unreliable, content (probably true for the majority population, but I
    doubt the anti-intellectual-property extremists would compromise on this
    point); and piracy won't starve the artist, since there's always demand
    for their work--just the publishers who can't adapt to new distribution
    models.
  </comment>
</link>

</linkfarm>
